www.ady.ng 2019-05-02

# Privacy Policy – Naijaturnup

**Privacy Policy**

 **Last update: March 2017**

 **Information we gather:**

The following information is gathered from our website visitors:  
IP address

 **How we use the information we gather:**

We use the information to enhance our site.

 **The people that are given access to this information:**

Your personal information is accessible by site administrators

 **The security measures we have in place to protect your personal information:**

To safeguard your personal information, please do not upload anything you want to keep private.

 **Use of cookies:**

Our website makes use of cookies which are small digital files that are stored in your web browser that enable us to track your return visits to our website.

Your browser settings may allow you to block these cookies, but we recommend you have them enabled to help us personalize your experience of our website.

 **What is a cookie and what does it do?**

Cookies are messages that web servers pass to your web browser when you visit Internet sites. Your browser stores each message in a small file, called cookie.txt . When you request another page from the server, your browser sends the cookie back to the server.

 **Why do we use cookies?**

It is mostly used by Web Server as an ID that was used to identify YOU from others. It is also used by program (eg. JavaScript) to store a temporal data used in the program itself.

 **What is a cookie policy?**

The Cookie Law is a piece of privacy legislation that requires websites to get consent from visitors to store or retrieve any information on a computer, smartphone or tablet. Almost all websites use cookies – little data files – to store information in people’s web browsers.

 **Are Cookies secure?**

Cookies that are sent over HTTP (port 80) are not secure as the HTTP protocol is not encrypted. Cookies sent over HTTPS (port 443) are secure as HTTPS is encrypted. So, if Facebook sends/receives cookies via HTTP, they can be stolen and used nefariously. That’s why you should always check for a green padlock right beside your browser’s url bar. A website without a green padlock is insecure and all data that are sent and received can be hijacked with Man-in-the-middle attack.

 **Are Cookies bad?**

No, cookies are stored in txt files which will never cause any trouble to your device.
